DAVID CASTILLO MORA - BILINGUAL (ENGLISH / SPANISH)

Python | Java | C# | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Oracle Cloud | SQL Server Davidcm2803@gmail.com - 64402488

Summary

Technical Support Specialist with 3+ years of experience in high-volume customer service and technical support. Extensive experience in resolving hardware and software issues, including system diagnosis, repair, and optimization. Proven ability to quickly identify and resolve technical failures, ensuring efficient and continuous equipment performance.

Here is my own portfolio, check it out so you can get to know me better. https://portafolio-david-roan.vercel.app/

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS: - Effective Communication - Teamwork - Problem Solving - Adaptability - Time Management - Empathy - Leadership - Critical Thinking - Interpersonal Skills - Creativity

TECHINAL SKILLS: - Python - Java - C# - PhP - JavaScript - HTML - CSS - Oracle Cloud - SQL Server - Linux commands

EXPERIENCE

CALL CENTER

Amazon CRC 2021-2022

Assisted U.S. Amazon employees with Covid-19 medical leave requests, ensuring timely claim approvals and benefits, leading to higher employee satisfaction and streamlined processes.

- Gained expertise in soft skills, including empathy, improved English communication (oral and written), and managed a high volume of calls and cases.
- Enhanced call quality by empathetically addressing employee concerns and optimizing processes to better meet customer needs.
- Achieved a 30% improvement in handle time, enabling the resolution of twice as many cases within the same time frame, along with strong customer satisfaction metrics.

TECHINAL SUPPORT

Shyft Global Services 2022-Currently

Back Office Support Specialist, I assist field engineers by providing in-depth support in troubleshooting hardware and software issues, as well as sourcing and requesting technological parts for customers in the United States.

- Developed expertise in technological parts, inventory processes, and software troubleshooting by collaborating closely with field engineers and made me learn teamwork.
- Streamlined processes for creating cases and requesting parts, significantly reducing response times and improving efficiency.
- Enhanced team metrics optimized global inventory management, and improved service delivery for customers in the US, Canada, and Japan.

EDUCATION

Centro Educativo Adventista Bilingue de Costa Rica

2015-2020

• High School Diploma

Centro Cultural Británico

2020-2021

• English Studies B2+

Universidad Centroamericana de Ciencia y Tecnología

2022-Currently

• System Engineering

CERTIFICATES

- Java esencial
- Fundamentos de matemática: Aplicaciones útiles en tu día a día
- Java avanzado 2

- Aprende C#
- C#: Programación orientada a objetos
- Mindfulness for Beginners